const quizQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'What is the capital of Egypt?',
    type: 'mcq',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Cairo',
      options: [
        'Cairo',
        'Alexandria',
        'Luxor',
        'Aswan',
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'do you love me?',
    type: 'true_false',
    answers: {
      answer: true,
      options: [
        true,
        false,
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'do you love me?',
    type: 'true_false',
    answers: {
      answer: false,
      options: [
        true,
        false,
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'do you love me?',
    type: 'true_false',
    answers: {
      answer: true,
      options: [
        true,
        false,
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'do you love me?',
    type: 'true_false',
    answers: {
      answer: false,
      options: [
        true,
        false,
      ],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'whats my name',
    type: 'short_answer',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Zaher',
      options: [],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'whats my name',
    type: 'short_answer',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Zaher',
      options: [],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    quiz_id: 'quiz-1',
    question: 'whats my name',
    type: 'short_answer',
    answers: {
      answer: 'Zaher',
      options: [],
    },
    quiz_title: 'Quiz 1',
    quiz_mark: 10,
    quiz_time: 5,
  },
];

export {
  quizQuestions,
};
